Guide to the New-York Historical Society Audiovisual Media Record Group 1974-2002 NYHS-RG 28
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Audiotapes, 1974-1991; 3.46 Linear feet
  - Belknap Training, 1988 November 15 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Ruth Bowman and Mary Munley. Second Docent Training, 1987 November 9 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Ruth Bowman. Training Session, 1987 November 2 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - John Brademas. New York: University in the City., 1987 March 11 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Ella Foshay Lecture.Thomas Cole, undated (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Tim Burgard. Course of Empire Training (2 tapes), 1989 January 31-February 1 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Luman Reed, undated (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Art Reveals History. Tim Burgard and Deborah Gardner, 1990 October 10 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Cory Munson. Life in British Colonial New York, 1986 August (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Carole Slatkin. Audubon Training: Breeding Birds of New York State, 1987 November 18 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Carole Slatkin. Audubon Training: Selected Breeding Birds of New York State, 1987 October 6 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Carole Slatkin. Audubon, 1986 December 10 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Audubon. Training for Children's Tour (2 tapes), undated (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Audubon Calls, 1990 February (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Audubon Bird Calls, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Audubon Bird Songs and Calls. Fall Migrants and Winter Residents, undated (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Blue Bird Society Orchestra, undated (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Thomas Bender Lecture, 1987 April 1 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Training Session, 1988 March 8 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
    Outside label reads General Background Monique Richards.
  - Dr. Sherene Baugher Lecture. Digging to the Core of the Big Apple: Under New York with an Archaeologist., 1988 April 14 (Offsite-box 9, Cassette -)
  - Introduction to Department of Public Programs: Highlights for Teachers, 1986 June 25 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - The Changing Face of American Portraiture Tour, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - The Rise and Fall of New York Training, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - George Washington Training (2 tapes), 1989 April 25 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Mary Alice. Tour of N-YHS Collection, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Ella Foshay. Niagara Docent Training, 1986 January 28 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Boccherini Ensemble: A New Direction, 1990 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Produced by Jon Mishne and John Madeski.
  - Boccerini Ensemble Live: Robert J. Lurtsema, 1991 January 16 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    W.G.B.H. Morning Pro Musica.
  - Why History? Historical Perspectives:Race and Class in New York City (2 tapes), 1991 February (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Roberta Olson Lecture. T.J.Bryan, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Wade McCann. Tiffany, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Annie Dillard Lecture, 1988 October 25 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - The Great Experiment. Pulse, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Muriel Hobson. Silver Tour, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - William H. Gerdts Lecture. What was American About American Art? National Aspirations and Iconic Devolution, 1992 April 22 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - New York City [illegible] Lecture, 1992 June 23 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Evelyn Hershey. Wilkinson Toy Show Training, 1986 October 14-15 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #1-2 (5 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Contains the episodes: The Thirteen States in 1787 and Need for a New Government Plan in 1787.
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #3-4 (3 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Consists of episodes Conflicts and Compromises and The Grand Convention-Who Was There.
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #5-6 (2 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Consists of episodes: How Should Congress Be Organized and A Constitution By and For The People.
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #7-8 (2 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Consists of episodes: Executive and Judicial Functions and Thirteen Contests for Ratification.
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #9-10 (2 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Consists of episodes: The Creation of the Bill of Rights and The Ever-Changing Constitution.
  - Dr. James Mooney. Putting New York on the Map, 1988 November 1 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - John K. Roth Lecture. What is the American Dream?, 1992 April 16 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
    Label reads Tape 2 of 2. Missing Tape 1.
  - Wagstaff Silver Collection, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Arnold Newman Lecture, 1988 October 19 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Scott Simon Lecture, 1988 September 28 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Ted Morgan Lecture. F.D.R., 1986 November 5 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Frederick Wiseman Lecture, 1988 October 5 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Edmund Morris Lecture, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Friends of the Library, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Martha Roster: Video, Myth, and American Media, 1992 April 29 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - [Koren] Lecture, 1988 October 12 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Robert Glenn Ketchum Lecture, 1987 May 12 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - James Bell: Niagara Falls, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - A House Divided, 1990 February 4 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Ella Foshay. Hudson River School Gallery Tour, 1985 September 13 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Ella Foshay. Hudson River School Docent Training, 1987 December 1 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Joel Rapp Program. Arthur Marks Interview, 1987 October 10 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Century Club, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Radio Interviews, 1990 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Whose History? Tape Two (3 copies), undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Angela Brown, Soprano. Recital of American Song, 1988 November 12 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Panel Discussion. Promised Land:The American Indian and the West, 1990 February 25 (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Friends of the Library, undated (Offsite-box 10, Cassette -)
  - Nell Painter. Sojourner Truth and the Forging of a Distinctly American Religion, 1992 April 8 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Adult Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - City Hall Lecture, 1992 June 11 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Ted Morgan Lecture, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - The N-Y Buenos Aires Connection: Argentinean Tango (Tape 2), undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Evan W. Cornog Lecture. City Hall and New York's Hopes: The Public Face of the Empire City, 1992 June 18 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - New York in the 21st Century, [1992] April 27 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Responsibility, Change, and Power (2 copies), undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Responsibility, Change, and Power (Q & A) # 2, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Richard Bushman Lecture. Writing History: Works and Process, 1992 November 12 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Donald L. Fixico Lecture. Writing History: Works and Process, 1992 November 19 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Lizabeth Cohen Lecture. Writing History: Works and Process, 1992 December 1 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Nell Painter Lecture. Writing History: Works and Process, 1992 December 17 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Jazz Des Jeunes #2, 1991 March 9 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Life and Survival in the City # 1, 1991 April 24 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - The Clarke Tin Whistle Handbook Companion Tape, 1988 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Mario T. Garcia (2 tapes), 1992 April 1 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Schama, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Dr. Benjamin Hook Lecture. Minorities and The Constitution., undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - James Tuttleton Lecture. Reshaping the Image of Columbus, 1992 January 8 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Monique Richards. Bellows, Bobbins, and Butter Churns, 1988 March 23 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
    Radio program on WMCA-AM.
  - David Woodward Lecture. The Aesthetics and History of Cartography, 1991 November 14 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Irma B. Jaffe. The Italian Presence at the World's Columbian Exposition in Chicago 1893, 1992 January 23 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Forum on History Centers (3 tapes), 1995 May 20 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Prejudice and The Other New Yorker (Tape 2), [1991] May 8 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - John K. Roth Lecture. What is the American Dream? (Part 1 of 2), 1992 April 16 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Images of the City #2, 1991 March 3 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Wilcomb E. Washburn Lecture. The Meaning of Discovery, 1991 December 11 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - James McPherson Lecture. Writing History:Works & Progress, 1993 January 7 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Studio Museum Trip, 1989 December 13 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Charles Musser, 1992 March 25 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Dave Sear Live, 1987 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
    Steamboat Productions.
  - Evelyn Hershey. Wilkinson Toy Show Training, 1986 October 15 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Adult Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Mary Woods Lecture. Between Art and Politics: A History of the [Architecture] Profession, 1991 July 9 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Remington Training, 1985 November 13 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - David Tatham Lecture. Frederick Remington, 1985 November 17 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Richard Pena Lecture. How Hollywood Movies Could Be Un-American, 1992 June 4 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Paris 1889: Americans at the Fair, [1989?] (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
    Lecture presented by Carol Troyen and Pat Mainard.
  - Nielson Quintet, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - WNCN Radio: Virtuosi Quintet "Inside the Music", 1987 February 15 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - The Capriccio Ensemble, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Silver Vaughn, 1987 May 20 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Press Conference, 1990 January 24 (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Whose History?, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
    Label reads Tape 2.
  - Children Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - New York Strings. Grieg: Moltezosuite First 2, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Race and Class in New York. Historical Perspectives (Tape 1), [1991] (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Springstead Sextet, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - The Homefront: While They Fought, undated (Offsite-box 11, Cassette -)
  - Elizabeth McKinsey Lecture. Niagara: America's Natural Monument, 1986 February 2 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Nina Gray Lecture. Toys, 1989 December 12 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Lisabeth Cohen Lecture. Re-examining the Melting Pot: What "Being American" Meant to a "Nation of Immigrants", 1992 May 27 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - N-YHS 60 Second Radio Announcement, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Arnold Newman Feature: Around New York (2 tapes), 1988 September 20 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - N-YHS Exhibit: "Art What Though Eat", 1990 December 17 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Jasper Cropsey, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Ella Foshay Lecture. Treasures of the N-YHS, 1988 July 19 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - David Howard Lecture. New York and the China Trade, 1984 February 26 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Washburn Lecture. Columbus, 1991 November 12 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Ellen Young Audition Tape, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Odyssey Chamber Players, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Dr. Folts Lecture. Justice Rendered, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Richard Lewis Lecture. Audubon, 1990 April (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Annette Blaugrund Lecture. The Taste of Andrew Carnegie, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Paul Candide. "Oh Lady of New York Harbor" (The Statue of Liberty), undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Images of the City # 1, 1991 March 3 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Voices to Be Heard, 1991 May 5 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - The NMAA Symposium. Panel Discussion: Afternoon Speakers (4 tapes), 1992 March 6 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
    [National Museum of American Art].
  - Annette Blaugrund Lecture. Paris 1889, [1989?] (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #3-4, [1987] (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #5-6 (2 copies), [1987] (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #7-8, [1987] (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #8-9 (2 copies), [1987] (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Ansel Adams Photographs (lecture), 1992 September 10 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Party-TIME, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Robert Peck Lecture. Audubon in Context, 1986 April 9 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Robert Peck Lecture. 300 years of American Bird Painting, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Dorothy Gallanter. Catesley, Wilson, & Audubon, 1985 November 10 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - David Lane [Lank] Lecture. Audubon, 1985 May 5 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Esther Pasztory Lecture. MesoAmerica: The Unexpected Civilization, 1991 December 5 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Sol Wachter Lecture, [1991] October 21 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - [Patricia Limerick], 1992 May 12 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
    Patricia Limerick's name is crossed over on the label.
  - Alfonso Ortiz Lecture. Beyond Corn, Beans, and Squash: The Impact of the New World on the Old, 1992 January 15 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - John Noble Wilford Lecture. Discovering Columbus, 1991 November 18 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Jean Ashton. Library Training Session, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - No House, No Home, 1991 April 21 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Music from China, 1991 April 20 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Harold Jaffe, undated (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Ron LaFrance. Native American Spirituality, 1992 May 19 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Contemporary Issues (2 tapes), 1991 February 23 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Mosette Broderick Lecture. Mckim, Mead and White: Transform NY, 1991 June 18 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Life and Survival in the City # 2, 1991 April 24 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - James McPherson Lecture. Writing History: Works amd Process, 1993 January 7 (Offsite-box 12, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Responsibility, Change, and Power # 1 (3 copies), 1991 April 10 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Responsibility, Change, and Power # 2 (2 copies), 1991 April 10 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Los Pleneros de la 21 # 1 (4 copies), 1991 March 23 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Los Pleneros de la 21 #2 (3 copies), 1991 March 23 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - [Why History? Race and Class] Cornel West Lecture. The Role of Visionary Leadership (3 tapes), 1991 February 5 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - N-YHS: Rhythms of New York (samples), undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Duane Duvalle, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - The Great Experiment. Pulsed (2 copies), [1987] (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
    The Constitution.
  - Books in Library, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Betsy McCaughey Lecture. The Constitution, 1987 October 14 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - McCann's New York WMCA Radio. Arthur Marks on Walking, 1987 August 23 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Bridging the Gap (2 tapes), 1991 March 27 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Prejudice and The Other New Yorker (Tape 1), 1991 May 8 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Jazz des Jeunes #1, 1991 March 9 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Ken Jackson Lecture. Robert Wagner, 1988 April 27 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Donna Wissinger, Flute, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
    Program is included in the cassette case.
  - Why History? Life and Survival in the City # 1, 1991 April 24 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Historical Perspectives:Race and Class in New York City (2 tapes), 1991 February 13 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Calabria Bella, 1991 February 23 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? New to the City, 1991 April 7 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Contemporary Issues, 1991 February 27 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - CUNY: US Constitution on the Air #9-10, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Russell [Berk]. JJA, 1986 September 21 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Mary Argenti and Madeline Morton-Mueller. Victorian Parlor Music, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
    Label reads Upstairs/Downstairs.
  - Vieuxtemps-Scherzo in D minor. Ravel-Tzigane., undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Doreen Dasilva and Mimi Stern Wolfe, 1988 January-February (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Charleston String Quartet, 1984 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Alexander and Daykin. Piano Duo, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - BBC Radio. Dowland, Britten, & Vaughan Williams, 1982 October 14 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - N-YHS Concerts. WBAI Radio Interviews: Virtuosi Quintet, 1988 January (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Mellory K. Matthews. Singer, 1986 November 21 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Polish Theatre Institute Music. "In Pursuit of Liberty", undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Prof. Leuchtenberg Lecture, undated (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - National Public Radio Broadcasts: Cherish the Ladies, 1987 (Offsite-box 13, Cassette -)
  - Luce 1, undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - No labels (13 tapes), undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
    These tapes have no labels or other identifying information on them.
  - OTL Second Hour, 1990 March 19 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - R & C [Training] Meeting, undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Bierstadt. Susan Sivard:Volcanoes, 1991 April 12 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Annette Blaugrund. "All Things Considered", 1990 May 30 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Paris Symposium, [1989?] (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Robert Stern Lecture, 1987 March 18 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - IBM: Salute to the Arts, 1987 September 9 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
    Presented on WQXR.
  - Government By Choice (3 copies), [1987] (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
    Label reads # 1181.
  - Why History? Bridging the Gap # 1 and 2 (6 tapes), 1991 March 27 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - [Rudigll] minus first 25 minutes, undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - WOR Sports: Rachel Robinson, undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Jacques Bablon "With Thanks", undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
    Label reads U.S.Information Agency- Voice of America.
  - N-YHS Introduction:America's Past Colonial Life, Paintings, Audubon, Tiffany (2 copies), undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - N-YHS: Jackie Robinson (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
    Label also reads William Altman Advertising.
  - Thomas Bender Lecture. Are Cities American?, 1992 May 21 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - "Made for Each Other", undated (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Why History? No House No Home (2 copies), 1991 April 21 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Images of the City (2 tapes), 1991 March 3 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Calabria Bella # 1 and 2 (8 tapes), 1991 February 23 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Contemporary Issues (2 tapes), 1991 February 23 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Cornel West Lecture. The Role of Visionary Leadership, 1991 February 5 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Why History? Life and Survival in the City, 1991 April 24 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Voices to be Heard, 1991 May 5 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Jazz Des Jeunes # 1 and 2 (8 tapes), 1991 March 9 (Offsite-box 14, Cassette -)
  - Lee Graham Interviews: James Heslin, Director of N-YHS. (Cartridge, tape), 1974 October 30 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    Tape reel # U-683. Interview of Heslin by WNYC/93.9 FM/TV/31. Aired January 1975.
  - Government by Choice PSAs (open reel, tape), 1987 September 14 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    Label for 7 1/2 ips ft mono reads :30 & :60 PSA's for N-YHS's "Government By Choice."
  - N-YHS Adult/Child Narrative (4 open reels, tape), 1987 March 10 (Offsite-box 17, Reel -)
    This is likely the introduction to N-YHS and its collections produced in 1986-87. Consists of four open reels with the identifying number S-7761 on each. There are three 15 feet reels labeled Outs (Dolby), Pulsed Mixes (Endless Loop), and Adult/Child Slide Narration. One reel is labeled Mix 7 Voice 5. 3 reels appear to be audio; the fourth is uncertain and might be the slides to accompany the narrative.
  - The Great Experiment / Constitution Slide Show (3 open reels, tape), 1987 September 11 (Offsite-box 17, Reel -)
    Consists of three open reels with the identifying number T-9912 on each. The reels are labeled N-YHS Constitution 'Outs', "Constitution" Narrative Pulsed, and the third is labeled "The Great Experiment" and contains a typed script with annotations. The first two reels are audio; the third is uncertain but might be the slide show.
- Series III. Digital Media, circa 1980s-2002; 0.36 Linear feet
  The items are in no particular arrangement.
  The series includes a small number of digital formats. The most useful is the 2002 DVD concerning a tribute to N-YHS honorees Colin and Nancy Campbell. The bulk of the series includes 5-1/4 inch floppy disks, many of which appear to be operating system or other software applications for personal computers.
  - In Trust to America: A Tribute to Colin and Nancy Campbell, 2002 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    Produced by the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, this 9 minute DVD film celebrates the awarding of the N-YHS's DeWitt Clinton Medal to the Campbells. DVD features Society President Kenneth T. Jackson and was screened at the History Makers Gala in 2002.
  - The Making of Alice in Wonderland, [2009] (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    Disk contains the numbers 2009.39 and 2009.40, possible Museum object numbers.
  - Backup Multi Lotus Inventory (8 floppy disks), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    Consists of 5-1/4 inch disks. Disks appear to be software programs and are individually labeled Formatted DSK 31-34, Backup System Backup, PC Tools Backup, and DOS 3.2.
  - Software Etc. (10 floppy disks), circa 1980s? (Offsite-box 15, Folder -)
    Consists of 5-1/4 inch disks. Several disks are labeled as Invoices, D-Base, Whi and Mo Bkup.The remainder are unlabeled.
  - Documents (9 floppy disks), Before Fiscal Year 1993 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    Consists of 5 1/4 inch disks. Disks are individually labled as: N-YHS Emergency Plan Draft, Labels/Exhibition, Technical Services Job Description, Correspondence, and Budget Table.